...and that's why
you keep coming.
并且那就是为什么你一直到来
That's why He keeps reminding you,
"Hey, I am here, long for Me!"
那就是为什么祂一直提醒你 嗨 我在这里 渴望我
Be a little wise at least.
至少变得智慧一点
Then you say, "Aaaah, yeah, but I like this
world. It's so beautiful, but I like You also.
接着你说 啊哈 是的 但是我喜欢这个世界 它是如此的美丽 但是我也喜欢你
When I have some time,
I can dedicate myself to You
当我有些时间的时候 我可以向你奉献我自己
or when I get grey hair on my
head I can give some time to You.
或者当我有一头白发的时候我可以留些时间给你
When I finish my duty,
当我完成我的责任时
when I finish work, you know, I have time,
then I can give some time to You."
当我完成工作时 我有时间 然后我可以留些时间给你
You see, God "also",
神 也
but in reality, it
should be "only" God,
但实际上 只应该是神
because He is the
only one which is real.
因为祂是唯一的真实
All others are not.
其实都不是
But people don't like
to hear that, no?
但是人们不喜欢听到那 不是吗
People like to hear
that everything is fine,
人们喜欢听到一切都很好
everything is okay.
万事如意
You know, you ask somebody, "How
are you?" "Oh, fine Swamiji! All good!"
你问某人 你怎么样 哦 很好 尊者吉 一切都很好
Whatever. Who
are you fooling?
无论怎样 你是在愚弄谁
Yourself!
你自己
I always take an example,
somebody comes and says,
我已经举一个例子 某人来到并说
"I love you!" And then you say,
"Oooh, I love you too!"
我爱你 然后接着你说 哦 我也爱你
"I love you so much
I can give my life for you!"
我非常爱你 我可以为你献出我的生命
You hear that, no?
Yes or no? [Yes.]
你听到那 不是吗 是还是不是
You have heard it also
many times? [No.]
你也听到过很多次
One time, two times.
"I'd give my life for you!"
一次 俩次 我可以为你献出我的生命
And you are happy
to hear that, "Oh,
你听到那很快乐 哦
he will give his life for me!
He loves me so much!"
他将为我献出他的生命 他非常爱我
Inside your soul says,
你内在的灵魂说
"I have fooled him." The other one says
- the one who said, "I'll give my life"
我已经骗过他了 那个人说 - 说过我将献出生命的人
says, "Ah, look at this
idiot, he believes me!",
说 啊哈 看着这个傻瓜 他相信我
you know, and that's
the game you all play.
那就是你们都玩的游戏
Knowingly or unknowingly
you are fooling each other,
故意或者无意 你在愚弄对方
you are playing the same
drama towards each other
你们之间上演着同样的戏剧
because you have fooled
yourself in believing that.
因为通过相信那你已经愚弄了自己
And then you think that you
are fooling somebody else?
并且认为你在愚弄其他人
No, my dear!
不 我亲爱的
You are making the
greatest fool of yourself.
你在最大程度的愚弄自己
How long would you
play that fooling game?
你还能玩那愚蠢的游戏多久
Maybe you will say, "Yes, this
Swamiji is very rude, you know,
你可能会说 是的 这个尊者吉非常粗鲁的说出那
to say that",
I don't care,
我不在乎
I am here to
say the truth.
我在这里是说出事实的
You want to hear it, you hear it,
you don't want to hear it, don't hear it.
你听你想听的 不听你不想听的
Many lives. I am
just a reminder.
很多世 我只是个
What I have attained,
I want you all to attain,
我所达到的我希望你都能达到
but I can't do it for you.
但不能为你做那
You have to do it.
你必须自己去做
When you truly long for it,
everything will come to you.
当你真正的渴望那 所有东西都会来到你身边
When there is not this fooling
game, everything will flow to you,
当不是渴望这愚蠢的游戏时 所有东西都会跟随你
automatically. God didn't say that you
should let go of everything, you know,
自动的 神不会说你应该放下一切
and just concentrate
on Him. No, He said, "No,
并仅仅专注于祂 不 他会说 不
I am in everything, yes,
I have given you, take!
我在万物之中 是的 我已经给你了 拿着
Do your duty,
做你的义务
but let your mind
be upon Me."
但让你头脑专注于我